okay so now that we have seen how
register naming Works let's try it
ourselves so let's have a register
naming
quiz okay so we will have a rat here
that will tell us where the values for
R1 R2 R3 R4 R5 and R6 are and over here
we will have a sequence of instructions
as they're fetched and then we will need
to write in what's renamed okay so here
we have the initial state of the Rat
which is simply R1 is mapped to P1 R2 to
P2 Etc and here are our instructions in
order to help you get started I'm going
to rename the first instruction so after
renaming it's still a
multiplication R2 and R2 are P2 and P2
R2 is where we should put our value and
remember we need to rename it in the red
so it's going to be in
p7 so this is what this renamed
instruction looks like read registers
physical registers P2 and P2 and put the
result in p7 now it's your turn you need
to both tell me what's renamed and also
update the rat
accordingly